postcron.com 2018-09-05

# Postcron - Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy

Effective as of May 24, 2018.

#### Summary

1\. Introduction – Postcron Privacy Policy  
2\. Personal Information we may collect  
3\. Personal Information provided by You  
4\. Use of Social Networks User Data  
5\. Use of Contact Information  
6\. Log Data  
7\. Cookies and Automatically Collected Information  
8\. Third Party Web Beacons and Third Party Buttons  
9\. Information Sharing and Disclosure  
10\. Security  
11\. Links to Other Websites  
12\. Data Transfer  
13\. Our Policy Towards Children  
14\. Your rights  
15\. Changes to this Policy  
16\. How to contact us  

### 1\. Introduction – Postcron Privacy Policy

Postcron provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information received from users (“Personal Information”) of this website, located at postcron.com ("Site"), as well as all related websites, applications, and other services provided by us (collectively, together with the Site, our “Service”). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Postcron Terms and Conditions.

This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your Personal Information, and how you can reach us to update your contact information or get answers to questions you may have about our privacy practices.

The aim of this Policy is to:

Ensure that you understand what Personal Information we collect about you, the reasons why we collect and use it, and who we share it with;

Explain the way we use the Personal Information that you share with us in order to give you a great experience when you are using the Service; and

Explain your rights and choices in relation to the Personal Information we collect and process about you and how we will protect your privacy.

We hope this helps you to understand our privacy commitments to you. For information on how to contact us if you ever have any questions or concerns, please see the ‘How to Contact Us’ Section 16 below. Alternatively, if you do not agree with the content of this Policy, then please remember it is your choice whether you want to use the Postcron Service.

### 2\. Personal Information We May Collect

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We obtain Personal Information relating to you from various sources described below.

Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

### 3\. Personal Information Provided By You

#### Registration

If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site or request to receive marketing materials, you may be required to become a registered user, and to submit the following types of Personal Information to Postcron: your name, email address, full user name, and time zone.

#### Customer Support

We may collect information through your communications with our customer support team or other communications that you may send us and their contents.

#### Making a Purchase

When you make payments through the Service, you will need to provide Personal Information such as your credit card number and billing address to the third party you choose to pay the Service. Please remember that Postcron does not processes payments and, thus, the Personal Information relating to payment (such as credit card details) do not need to be provided to us.

#### Social Media

In order to allow you to post to your social media platforms, we may ask you to provide your username, account ids, social handle, timezones, and email address.

#### Other

We may also collect your contact details when you provide them in the context of our customer, vendor, and partner relationships.

### 4\. Use of Social Networks User Data

If you connect your third party social media account to your Postcron account, we may collect certain information stored in your social media account such as:

#### Facebook

Postcron may allow you to connect a Facebook page, profile, groups or events to your Postcron account, in which case we will access certain information from Facebook regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / page ID or profile ID, access tokens, sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Postcron to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### Twitter

Postcron may allow you to connect a Twitter profile to your Postcron account, in which case we will access certain information from Twitter regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post, to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Postcron to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### Pinterest

Postcron may allow you to connect a Pinterest page or profile to your Postcron account, in which case we will access certain information from Pinterest regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, sent posts, and profile boards. This includes the content of your post, to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Postcron to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### LinkedIn

Postcron may allow you to connect a LinkedIn profile to your Postcron account, in which case we will access certain information from LinkedIn regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post, to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Postcron to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### Google+.

Postcron may allow you to connect a Google+ page or profile to your Postcron account, in which case we will access certain information from Google regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post, to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Postcron to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

### 5\. Use of Contact Information

In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please un-follow us, or follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. **You may also opt out from receiving commercial email from us by sending your request to us by email at[support@postcron.com](mailto:support@postcron.com).** Please be aware that if you opt out of receiving commercial email from us or otherwise modify the nature or frequency of promotional communications you receive from us, it may take a reasonable time but no longer than ten business days for us to process your request, and you may continue receiving promotional communications from us during that period. Additionally, even after you opt out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service.

### 6\. Log Data

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site’s technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service.

### 7\. Cookies and Similar Technologies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. **We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information.** Postcron may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services.

A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential. Postcron does not process or respond to web browsers’ “do not track” signals or other similar transmissions that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who use our Service.

We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message. This information is gathered from all users, and may be connected with other information about you.

### 8\. Third Party Web Beacons and Third Party Buttons

We may display third-party content on the Service, including third-party advertising. Third-party content may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms for obtaining data in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Service. Additionally, we may implement third party buttons (such as the Facebook “share” button) that may function as web beacons even when you do not interact with the button. Information collected through third-party web beacons and buttons is collected directly by these third parties, not by Postcron. Information collected by a third party in this manner is subject to that third party’s own data collection, use, and disclosure policies.

### 9\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

Our primary purpose for using your information is to publish your content on social platforms. In addition, we may share and disclose your information for the following reasons:

#### Service Providers

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

#### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Postcron cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas),to protect Postcron against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.

#### Business Transfers

Postcron may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

#### Other Third Parties

We may make certain aggregated, automatically-collected, or otherwise non-personal information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality available through the Service.

### 10\. Security

Postcron is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to appropriately protect your Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Information in our possession.

Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information about you will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our administrative, physical, and electronic safeguards, subject to requirements under applicable law to ensure or warrant information security.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on our Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system , and any other disclosures that may be required under applicable law.

We also take measures to delete your Personal Information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When determining the retention period, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrollment with our products or services, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

### 11\. Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and security practices, and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### 12\. Data Transfer

Postcron is based in the United States. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the United States. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### 13\. Our Policy Towards Children

The Site is not directed to persons under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@postcron.com](mailto:support@postcron.com). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 16.

If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### 14\. Your rights

You can contact us to obtain a copy of the Personal Information held about you by us. This may be subject to a fee not exceeding any prescribed fee permitted by applicable law, if any. You can also ask us to correct and, where relevant, erase that information. As mentioned above you have a right to change your email preferences at any time.

If you are a registered user of the Site, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us by going to postcron.com//settings#accountSettings or by e-mailing us at [support@postcron.com](mailto:support@postcron.com). Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. To avoid any misunderstanding, in the event the user requests that all Personal Information be deleted, then Postcron shall proceed in accordance with such request in reasonable time. **Please be aware that once you have deleted your account or any Personal Information within your account, Postcron will no longer hold that Personal Information and will thus be unable to restore it.**

You should be aware that Postcron acts as a conduit between our users and the various Supported Platforms and Third-Party Apps. In several instances, the content published via Postcron will not be in Postcron’s custody or control, and any content that has been shared by you through any Supported Platform or Third-Party Apps via the Services may continue to be available to third parties and the public at large, as this content is now under the control of the operators of the Supported Platforms and/or the Third-Party Apps.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

### 15\. Changes to this Policy

Postcron reserves the right, at any time, to modify or replace the Privacy Policy. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is available at <https://postcron.com/en/terms_conditions_privacy_policy>. Please check the Privacy Policy periodically for changes, though we will also notify you via email or another direct electronic communication method of any changes that, in our sole discretion, materially impact your use of the Services or the treatment of your Personal Information. Your use of the Services following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes. If you object to any changes, you may delete your account.

### 16\. How to contact us

If you have any thoughts or questions or requests about this Privacy Policy please let us know at [support@postcron.com](mailto:support@postcron.com).
